Jeremy Bacca Barquero

15 oct 1996 Single License B1 and A3 Tel: 7016-0434 / 8595-9491

San José Costa Rica

Email: jerebac@hotmail.com jbaccab@ucenfotec.ac.cr

PROFILE

More than 4 years of experience in the technology industry. His technical background allows him to understand client needs and development capabilities. He has also worked as an Angular developer with extensive experience in the process efficiency environment, as well as React, pattern design, methodologies of different processes. I consider myself a lover of new challenges.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Languages: JavaScript, typescript, HTML, CSS, SASS, LESS, AngularJS Angular 2-16, NodeJS, jQuery, bootstrap, Flex box, Ajax, gulp, MCU, MUI, MVC, ReactJS React Native VUE.js

Data Bases: MongoDB (Lab, Atlas) MySQL Cloudinary, AMS, Google Cloud Services Firebase Heroku push management, Airtable database.

Software Methodologies and others Git, GitHub, Gitkraken Jira, Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, Scrum Methodologies Kanban Scrumban, Trello, Zoom, Microsoft teams, Slack, typeform, Jotform, Zapier,

Repositories: Gitlab, GitHub bitbucket, Azure Devops platform projects

EXPERIENCE SKILLS

Work Experience Summary

2022-2024 Jazz Gaming Services (Business Solutions)

Job Role: Analyst Web Developer and technical leader Company location Costa Rica, San José Pavas Plaza Mayor 2

Summary: Analyze user requirements, design domain and solution model using MVC

methodologies the application using the angular technology and most common Angular Libraries Material design follow best practice and integrate design

patterns to solution. Create testing scripts.

Environment Angular8, 12, 14, 15. 16 IONIC Nodejs node modules typescript, OOP

Firebase esm2015 azure devops.

2022 La Creativería

Job Role: Analyst React Developer

Company location Costa Rica, San José Escalante

Summary: Analyze user requirements, design domain and solution model using MVC

methodologies the application using React technology and most common React Libraries MUI Material Follow best practice and integrate design patterns to solution. Create testing scripts, micromanagement and send weekly reports.

Environment ReactJS React Native Expo Nodejs node modules typescript, OOP Firebase

console MUI Design.

2018 - 2021 GOLDEN CR

Job Role: Angular Developer
Project Location Costa Rica, Santa Ana

Summary: Analyze user requirements, design domain and solution model using MVC

methodologies the application using Angular technology and most common Angular frameworks such as Bootstrap, Angular Material Follow Angular best practice and integrate design patters to solution. Create testing scripts, landing

pages and send weekly reports.

Environment Angular JS Angular 12 Gulp Nodejs node modules bower components bootstrap

typescript, OOP.

2016 - 2017 LOCALPETS&FAMILY

Job Role: Angular Developer

Project Location Costa Rica

Summary: Provide effective solutions with proven technologies for business requirements.

Analyze requirements, risks and impacts for business needs and demonstrate

solutions by effective analysis and design. Connect with databases with the client needs.

Environment Angular JS Angular 12 Nodejs node modules bootstrap typescript, OOP.

Database MongoDB, AMS, Cloudinary Google Cloud Services

EDUCATION, TRAINING & CERTIFICATIONS

Education

Universidad Cenfotec, San Jose Costa Rica Superior web developer technician Graduated 12/2015

Training

Cenfotec Software House (Cenfotec University) QA analyst (Cenfotec University)

La Creativería

Certified Scrum Training (Udemy)

Jazz Gaming Solutions

Azure devops and automatic deploys. (Udemy)

REFERENCES

Robin Aguilar IT Department (Golden CR) 8862-3444

Oswald Soza Software Engineer at Battalion Games 7121-9118